大西洋帝国
第三季 第四集
早知道你要停下来 我就不挂电话了
I'd have kept speaking had I known you'd stop.
我可以不停下
I don't have to.
我要走了
I'd better go.
他心情又不好了
He's in a bad humor again.
那你迟点也没关系
Well,then it won't matter if you're late.
对吧 跟屁虫先生
Will it,Mr. Poofles?
芝加哥
有新鲜面包卷 要来点吗
There's some fresh rolls if you want.
我喜欢罂粟籽 这是芝麻的
I like the poppy. These are sesame.
他怎么没去上学
Why ain't he at school?
肚子痛
Bellyache.
让我看看你 宝贝
Let me take a look at you,champ.
这是怎么回事
What the hell's this?
宝贝 一边玩去
Sonny,go play.
-妈妈在跟你说话呢  -玩去吧
-Hey,your ma's talking to you. -Go play.
一边玩去 去吧
Go play. Come on.
去吧
Go on.
昨天他回家就这样了 我问过校长了
He came home with it yesterday. I rang the headmaster.
有个新来的男孩 喜欢欺负人
Some new boy,he's a bully.
欺负一个耳聋的小孩吗
Picking on a kid almost stone-cold deaf?
阿尔 那是个聋哑学校 所以他才去那儿上学
They all are,Al. That's why he's there.
本性难移
Boys will be boys,
不管聋不聋
whether they can hear each other or not.
这孩子得坚强才行
Kid's got to toughen up.
要来了 要来了
Coming through. Coming through.
好了 请安静
All right,pipe down.
汤普森先生有话要说
Mr. Thompson wants a word.
大家可能已经知道
As some of you may know,
我们在塔博尔高地的联络人
our contact at Tabor Heights...
维克多 希寇斯治安官最近去世了
Sheriff Victor Sickles died recently
正如"大西洋城报"报道的一样
as a result of what the "Atlantic City Press"
死于一起悲惨事故
has deemed a tragic accident.
考虑到这场
Given as how the chief witness
悲剧的主要证人
to this unfortunate occurrence
是来自纽约的吉普 罗塞蒂先生
was a Mr. Gyp Rosetti of New York,
这事儿恐怕没这么简单
it's quite possible there's a bit more to the story.
既然如此 除非另行通知
That being the case,until further notice,
运给罗斯坦先生的货物都走备用线路
all shipments to Mr. Rothstein will use back roads only,
全部避开塔博尔高地
avoiding Tabor Heights altogether.
在一月中旬吗 路上全是冰
In the middle of January? The roads are sheets of ice.
我们去哪儿加油
And where are we gonna get gas?
这是你的问题 对吧
That's your problem,isn't it?
你确定要这么做吗
You sure this is a good idea?
你问他干什么
What the fuck you asking him for?
我觉得如果...
I just thought when it comes to...
如果怎么样 我已经说过怎么办了
You just what? I already said how it is.
好的 纳吉 抱歉
All right,Nuck. I'm sorry.
去塔博尔高地
Get up to Tabor Heights,
看看情况如何
find out what the fuck is going on.
遵命
Yes,sir.
你知道那条
You know that coast road
通往哈蒙德的海岸路吧
that heads through Hammond?
去那儿
Head up there,
看看路上的冰有多厚
check out the roads. See how icy they actually are.
-你知道我说的哪条路吧  -知道
-You know the one I mean. -Okay.
罗兰 史密斯怎么样了
What's being done about Rowland Smith?
-谁  -罗兰 史密斯
-Who? -Rowland Smith.
奈特 霍尼希的司机
Nate Honig's wheelman.
一起来打劫的混蛋
The sack of shit who robbed this place.
让曼尼 霍维茨去处理了
That job was left to Manny Horvitz.
那他人呢
Oh,where's he been lately?
我还不够忙吗
I don't have enough on my mind?
难道我还得亲自检查你的工作
I have to start checking your fucking work,too?
还要我操心吗
Make sure things are being handled?
没有下次了 先生
It won't happen again,sir.
找到这个人 如有必要 去找萨维奇探员
Find this guy. Use Agent Sawicki if you have to.
要牵扯联邦调查局吗
You want the feds involved?
给他报酬前 先让他出力
He's on the goddamn payroll. Make him earn it.
还有什么要说的
Any more second-guessing?
我马上去办
I'll get on it straightaway.
-纳吉 我能说句话吗  -什么事
-Nucky,can I have a word? -About what?
罗塞蒂的问题 塔博尔高地的事情
This Rosetti business,the whole Tabor Heights thing.
如果你有抱怨 去找米奇
If you've got a complaint,talk to Mickey.
我没有
I don't.
我现在回来了
It's just that I'm back now.
我知道
I'm well aware of that.
那别让我闲着 纳吉
Then let me earn,Nucky.
我听你的话 服了刑
I did my time like you asked.
有些事情先搞清楚
Let's get something straight.
仅仅让你坐牢
Allowing you to simply go to jail
是我给你的最后恩赐
is the last gift I'll ever give you.
用词太不恰当了
This is rather infelicitous language,isn't it?
-阴道  -这是医学用语
-Vagina? -It is a medical term.
我向来不喜欢这个词的读音
I've never enjoyed the sound of it.
我也不喜欢芽甘蓝
I've never liked brussels sprouts,
但我不否认它们的存在
but I don't deny they exist.
好独特的类比
What a peculiar analogy.
你喜欢什么术语
What term would you prefer?
整个领域都成问题
The entire area is problematical.
你应该知道 有些主题
You do acknowledge certain subjects
不用术语 是无法讨论的吧
would be difficult to discuss without it?
性交 受精 生育
Intercourse,fertilization,birth.
你不觉得自己很坏吗 医生
You imagine yourself quite wicked,don't you,Doctor?
坐在教室后面的顽童
The jackanapes at the back of every classroom,
误将自己的窃笑当做大智慧
mistaking his sniggering for the wit of the world.
你说的更像是我的表兄弟弗朗西斯
That sounds more like my cousin Francis.
"怀孕"
"Pregnant."
又一个问题领域吗
Another problematical area?
"妊娠"听起来更稳妥
"Gravid" has a noble ring.
她们能明白什么意思吗
Will they even know what that means?
你不是打算教给她们吗
Is it not your intention to instruct them?
"有孩子"
"With child"?
"月事"
"Monthly time."
连"月经"你也觉得不妥吗
You are at odds with "menstruation"?
-这可是很好的拉丁语  -令人遗憾的新词
-It's good Latin. -A regrettable neologism.
联邦儿童局已经
The Federal Children's Bureau
出版了一系列
has already published a series
产前保健书籍 用的就是"月经"
on prenatal care and "menstruation" is what they use.
政客们的草率 我不关心
The indiscretion of politicians is of no concern to me.
我会旁听课程
I will be attending the class
确保我的指示得到贯彻
to make sure my instructions are followed.
这些是
And these are?
给女士们的礼物
Gifts for the women.
"高洁丝"
"Kotex."
修女 是卫生棉
Sanitary napkins,Sister.
这种东西在商店里公开售卖吗
These are sold openly in stores?
新上市的产品
They are a relatively new product.
或许您可以留一包...
Perhaps you yourself...
希望我们的晚班学员不要这样敏感
let's hope our evening students aren't quite so sensitive.
看来你径直走进了我的陷阱
Looks like you've stepped straight into my trap.
什么
What?
就像我要逮捕你那样
You know,like I was gonna arrest you.
为什么逮捕我
Why would you do that?
开个玩笑而已
Just making a little joke.
汤普森先生很忙
Mr. Thompson's a busy man.
反正没事干 开开玩笑罢了
I have nothing better to do?
大白天转悠到这了 对吧
Came out here in the middle of the day,didn't you?
这是罗兰 史密斯的地方吗
Is this Rowland Smith's place or not?
费城官方人士说是
That's what the Philly office says.
你跟其他探员提过吗
You spoke to other agents about this?
就一个
Just the one
我信得过的
that I can trust.
你指被你收买的那个
You mean the one that's crooked.
貌似锁上了
Looks like it's locked.
多谢你的说明
Thanks for clearing that up.
罗兰 史密斯很忙啊
Rowland Smith's been a busy fella.
至少有一半是我们的
At least half of this is ours.
现在都是我们的了
It's all ours now.
确定他会来吗
You sure he's showing up?
这是他主要存货地点
This is his main drop.
你在费城的人这么说
Says your man in Philly.
他最清楚不过 不是吗
Well,he would know,wouldn't he?
他为何不去给史密斯通风报信
And what's stopping him from tipping Smith off?
为何要那样
Why would he do that?
因为他以前从没费心去抓史密斯
Because he's never bothered to catch him.
他来了告诉我
Call me when he gets here.
我会处理的 我保证
I'll take care of it. You've my word.
不需要把自己扯进来
You needn't involve yourself.
我是这么交代你的吗
Is that what I asked you?
你说过要低调行事
You've mentioned low profiles.
我只是服从
I'm trying to oblige.
去找找乐子吧
Go buy a personality.
让我把话说清
Let me get this straight.
罗塞蒂正加油 希寇斯靠着旁边的油泵
Rosetti's gassing up,Sickles is at the next pump.
他浑身泼满了汽油
He completely douses himself with gasoline.
然后不知见了什么鬼
Then for some fucking reason,
突然想要抽支烟
decides that it's a good time for a smoke.
那有什么差别
Look,what's the difference?
他生前是你的搭档
The man was your partner.
我的意思是 那无关紧要
What I'm saying is,it don't matter.
一切都在掌控中
The situation's being handled.
什么意思
Meaning what?
我们正在处理
Me and the boys,we're taking care of it.
你刚刚还说不能逮捕他们
You just said you couldn't arrest them.
我没有说要逮捕他们
I'm not talking about arresting them.
我说要处理他们
I'm talking about handling them.
我明晚有一批货过路 拉姆西警官
I got a load coming through here tomorrow night,Deputy Ramsey.
我现在是治安官了
I'm the sheriff now.
我还是有货要过路
And I still got a load coming through.
没问题 同往常一样
It's fine. Same as always.
你们安心做生意
You boys go about your business.
把外国佬交给我们
Leave these dagos to us.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
让他做本职工作 伊莱
Let the man do his job,Eli.
你不是天底下唯一的治安官
You ain't the only sheriff ever lived.
上车
Get in the car.
什么鬼东西
What the fuck is this?
现金 还能是什么
Cash. What do you mean?
粘糊糊的
It's sticky.
有点脏 不知道 我刚吃了东西
Little schmutz. I don't know,I just ate.
你的钱都一股臭气
Even your money reeks.
你说什么
Fuck you talking about?
偶尔抽空去好好刮个脸会死吗你
Would it kill you to pony up for a decent shave once in a while?
喷点儿桂香水
A little Bay Rum.
我过敏
Gives me a rash.
杰克 说真的
Jake,I'm serious.
你老婆怎么说的
I mean,what does your wife say?
"我当初为何没嫁给弥尔顿 科恩特雷格"
"Why didn't I marry Milton Korntragger?"
那你的妓女们呢
Your whores,then.
我花钱堵她们的嘴
I pay 'em not to notice.
到十八号的哈里森了
18th up to Harrison.
余下的钱今晚去收
I got the rest of my collections tonight.
-哪儿去  -撒尿
-Where you going? -Take a leak.
所以啤酒这么赚钱
That's why beer is so profitable.
我们不卖 只是出租
We don't sell it,we only rent it.
个人卫生 杰克
Personal hygiene,Jake.
是很要紧的
It makes a big impression.
"今天过得怎么样 亲爱的"
"How was your day,honey?"
我是爱她 可是我这一天过得什么样
I love her and all,but my day?
就是这事那事
This happened and then that happened
一件接一件 就那样
and then the next thing. That's the day.
等你好容易把这些都整...
Now you gotta go through this whole...
你好啊
Hi there.
别动
Don't move.
搜身
Check him.
打兔子用的
Just for coneys.
你是谁
Who are you?
我还要问你们呢
Ask you the same question.
我爸妈的朋友吗
You friends of my folks?
我们看上去像朋友吗
Do we look friendly?
你还不错 他就不好说了
You seem okay. Don't know about him,though.
他们不喜欢我晚餐迟到 所以...
They don't like it if I'm late for dinner,so...
-你的名字  -朗 钱尼
-What's your name? -Lon Chaney.
诺玛 塔曼吉
Norma Talmadge.
巴比 佩姬
Baby Peggy.
三人都是当时著名的电影演员
罗兰 史密斯
Rowland Smith.
你对孩子太凶了
You're mean to children.
你自以为很牛吗
Aren't you the dog's bollocks?
那是好事吗
Is that a good thing?
接丽嘉酒店
Yeah,I need the Ritz-Carlton.
原来从大西洋城上岸的货
What used to come up from Atlantic City
现在从这里走 直接从海上来
comes right through here,straight in off the ocean.
没有中间人
Cut out the middleman.
开船 装货 然后把货运到沙滩上
We sail out,load up,off-load here right on the beach.
得晚上行动
Gonna have to do it at night.
估计还需要些船
We'll probably need some boats,too.
我没干过这行 真抱歉
I'm new to this. I'm sorry.
你都和我们干了一年了
You've been with us a year.
我哪知道海上什么样 我是从扬克斯来的
What do I know about the ocean? I'm from Yonkers.
-打扰一下 小姐  -先生
-Excuse me,miss. -Sir?
总有一天 我要带你去后面
One of these days I'm gonna take you in the back,
教你怎么做酱
show you how to really make sauce.
但是我不会下厨
But I don't know how to cook.
你来搅拌 我来管火
You stir,I'll provide the heat.
能给我一根吗
Could I have one?
你多大了
How old are you?
下个月满十六岁
16 next month.
先生
Sir.
-你不该抽烟  -我不抽
-You shouldn't smoke. -I don't.
那你为何要烟
Then why do you want a cigarette?
尝尝什么感觉
See what all the fuss is about.
你想讨好我吗
You trying to charm me,kid?
那您高兴了吗
Is it working?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你又要打我了吗
You gonna hit me again?
这我不反对
I'm not opposed to it.
你知道我是谁吗 罗兰
You know who I am,Rowland?
老实回答
Answer straight.
你是纳吉 汤普森
You're Nucky Thompson.
有年圣诞 你送给我家一只火鸡
You gave us a Christmas turkey once.
那是哪年
When did I do that?
一九一四年
1914.
我当时六岁
I was six.
妈妈真是感激涕零
Boy,was Ma grateful.
你就这么报答我的
Is this how you thank me?
什么
How do you mean?
偷我的货
Stealing my merchandise.
您大概不会在乎吧
I guess I didn't think you'd mind.
你为什么这么想
Why the hell would you think that?
不知道 每次我在报纸上看到你
I don't know. Whenever I see you in the paper,
你貌似都很开心
it looks like you're having a good time.
无论如何 我没只偷您
Anyway,I didn't steal it all from you.
还偷了谁的
Who else?
很多都是费城瓦克西 戈登的
A lot of it belongs to Waxey Gordon in Philadelphia.
他也给你妈一只火鸡了吗
Did he give your mother a turkey,too?
没
Heck,no.
他是个骗子
He's a crook.
告诉我你想怎么办
Tell me what you want to happen here.
什么意思
What's that mean?
事情出乎意料
It's not as expected.
事情发展成这样 皆我之过
The fault's mine for letting it get this far.
我负全责 你不用脏了手
I'll take responsibility and your hands stay clean.
来抽一根
Have one on me.
给个火
Need a light.
你叫人来了吗
Expecting someone?
联邦探员 举起手来
Federal agents. Get your hands up.
快 举起手来
Get 'em up. Hands up.
伙计们 慢慢来 慢慢来
All right,boys. Nice and slow. Nice and slow.
去前面
Go around front. Go around front.
怎么回事 罗兰
What's the story,Rowland?
我也没想到
Beats me.
他们是费城的禁酒探员
They're Prohees out of Philly.
他们在跟踪我
They've kind of been following me.
你这小混蛋
Arsed-out little shit.
-我只是在说情况  -里面有你认识的吗
-Just trying to get a leg up. -You know any of them?
那个拿着散弹枪的高条子
That tall fed with the 12-gauge,
他是瓦克西 戈登手下的
he's in Waxey Gordon's pocket.
-还有呢  -他们肯定想来杀我
-Anything else? -Pretty sure they're here to kill me.
别胡扯了...
Enough with the bull...
天啊 不是我们...
Jeez,it's not our...
好了 上 快点了事
All right,let's go. Do what you have to do.
看好窗户 伙计们
Watch the windows,boys.
我去查地下室
I'm gonna check the cellar.
找到什么没
Anything?
蜘蛛网还有松鼠粪
Just cobwebs and squirrel turd.
松鼠粪
Squirrel turds?
那是老鼠屎
That's rat shit.
再来一杯
Hit me again.
我来帮多里奥先生拿东西
Picking up for Mr. Torrio.
来一小杯
Give me a short one.
是古兹克对吧 多里奥的人
Guzik,right? Torrio's man.
没错 我认识你吗
Yeah. I know you?
乔 米勒 我是迪恩尼 奥巴尼恩的人
Joe Miller. I'm with Deanie O'Banion.
好吧
Uh-huh. Okay.
-这儿啤酒更好 对吧  -怎么说
-Beer's better here,huh? -How's that?
南边的啤酒更好吧
I say the beer's better here down on the South Side?
我喝起来没差别
Tastes the same to me.
反正 不可相信水(美国谚语)
Well,can't trust the water anyway.
什么水
What water?
任何水 我不知道 我只是...
Any water. I don't know,I'm just...
你喝酒 我也喝
look,you drink,I'll drink.
我们好好相处
We're fine,right?
对 当然
Sure,we are.
你说迪恩 奥巴尼恩是骗子
You called Dean O'Banion a liar.
-什么  -那天在多里奥那
-Huh? -That day at Torrio's.
-我不是认真的...  -你体型大嘴也大
-I don't really... -You got a big mouth to match that big gut.
好好喝酒吧 乔
Enjoy your beer,Joe.
有你在这 一身臭气 我哪喝得下
How can I with the stink coming off of you?
不理我是吧 大块头
Walk away from me,Jumbo?
我在跟你说话 你这肥佬
I'm talking to you,you fat fuck.
来拿东西的吗
Came to collect?
来
Here.
再给你点
Have some more.
感觉怎么样
How you holding up,huh?
快 搬上去
Come on,get it on. Get it on.
抓紧 伙计们 时间很紧
Hurry it up,guys. We don't have all night.
真够慢的
Taking their sweet time.
等着吧
Wait it out.
如果他们又要下来查怎么办
And if they decide to look down here again?
我们是一根线上的蚂蚱了
Well,we're all in this together,ain't we?
童言无忌
The mouths of babes.
我们车上留了什么
What did we leave in the car?
没什么 我总是打理干净
Nothing. I always keep it clean.
-车牌呢  -在坦尼的名下
-The plates? -In Tunney's name.
估计他不会在乎了
Don't expect he'll much mind now.
如果你要的话 我有五十个
I got maybe 50 if you need any.
五十个什么
Got 50 what?
车牌 随时能换
License plates. Swap 'em around.
那样就没人能找到我们了
That way,they can't ever track us.
你就是这么干的是吧
That's your system,is it?
我自己想出来的
Worked it out myself.
那他们怎么还是找到你了
Then what are they doing out there?
凑巧吧 我猜
Just coincidence,I reckon.
还是挺厉害的 对吧
Pretty good run,though,huh?
真让人好奇
Kept us guessing.
其实也不难 如果你不介意我直说
Not that hard,really,if you don't mind me saying.
-怎么不难  -快点开车 放几枪
-Why's that? -Drive fast,flash the pistol.
谁愿意为了几箱酒丢了小命
I mean,who wants to get all killed over a few crates of booze?
没有人
No one.
我也是这么想的
That's how I see it,too.
不过奈特真惨
Shame about Nate,though.
他是我的搭档
He was my partner.
是吗 他怎么了
Oh,aye? What happened to him?
联邦探员抓到他了
Feds got him.
看来他没你这么走运
Guess he didn't have your luck.
有人搜过地下室吗
Anyone check the cellar?
汤普森先生
Mr. Thompson.
是的 我查过了
Yeah,I did.
那就再查查
Well,check it again.
纽约
你干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
照你说的做啊
Like you said.
只要一勺泻药 贝尼
One part laxative,Benny.
你想让他们拉满赫斯特大街吗
You want them shitting themselves all over Hester Street?
有什么发现吗
Anything?
我和查理有事要谈
Charlie and I need to talk.
是时候让我参与了
I think it's time I got included.
-凭什么  -我挺身而出
-Based on what? -I stepped up.
做了我该做的 也就是说我能留下来听
I did what I had to. That means I stay in the room.
你在大街上开了一顿乱枪
You shot your wad off in the middle of the street.
-我干掉了他们中的一个  -是迈耶干的
-They went back minus one. -Meyer did that.
-我掩护了他  -贝尼
-I fucking gave him cover! -Benny.
我们必然会商议此事
We are certainly gonna discuss this,
但不是现在 所以...
but not right now,so...
他召我去见他 今天中午
I'm summoned. At noon.
我和你一起去
I'll come with you.
迈耶 马塞里亚对你恨之入骨
Meyer,Masseria hates that shayna punim of yours.
尤其是现在
Now more than ever.
你要是去了 谁知道会发生什么事
You turn up,who knows where this goes?
他必须明白如今的趋势
He needs to understand the way the world's heading.
是你说要和解的
You're the one who said come to terms.
-那是以前  -你看
-That was before. -Well,you see?
这就是你的问题所在
This is the problem with you.
总是刚愎自用
Always very headstrong.
幸好有我在 能让你理智一点
Good thing I'm here to talk some sense.
给他百分之二 百分之五是底线
Offer two. Settle at five.
百老汇西部不动 格兰德南部不给
Nothing west of Broadway,nothing south of Grand.
还有吗
Anything else?
别坐在窗户边
Try not to sit by the window.
今晚十点
Tonight,10:00 P.M.
我们这边都准备好了
All set on our end.
这些客户真是难缠
Some tough customers,these boys.
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you want to do this?
觉得我会让你们自己玩吗
Think I'm gonna let you fellas have all the fun?
我们在加油站见面
We'll meet by the filling station.
把车停到后面 多带些绳子
Pull the truck around back and bring plenty of rope.
好的 让我来 让我来
All right,let me roll. Let me roll.
看看 都是我的
Look at that,baby. All mine.
打我 小硬汉 来啊
Hit me,tough guy. Come on.
来啊 打我
Come on,hit me.
来啊
Come on.
打我
Hit me.
来啊 小硬汉 打我啊
Come on,tough guy. Hit me.
来啊 这是什么 来 用点力
Come on. What was that,huh? Come on,hit me harder.
这都是什么 再用力点
What was that? Harder than that.
来 把手举起来 把手举起来
Come on,put your hands up. Put your hands up.
把手举起来 像这样放到脸前
Put your hands up. Like this in front of your face.
放在脸前
In front of your face like this.
好 准备出拳
Okay? And you're gonna throw your punch.
你要像这样出拳
You're gonna throw your punch like bang!
来啊 让我看看你有多少力量 来啊
Come on,let me see what you got. Come on.
来 打我啊
Come on! Hit me!
你要出拳 你要让别人欺负你吗
You got to hit me. You gonna let people bully you,huh?
来 打我啊
Come on and hit me,huh?
过来 来
Come here. Come here.
到我怀里来
Come here. Come here. Shh.
好了 儿子
It's okay,Sonny.
好了 好了
Shh. Come on. Shh.
没事了
It's okay. Shh.
没事了 到我怀里来
It's okay. Come here. Come here.
好了 好了
Come on. Shh.
有爸爸呢
Papa's got you.
是的 是 是 好的 太太
Yes. Yeah,yeah. Yes,missus.
谢谢
Thank you.
汤普森太太也不知道
Mrs. Thompson has no information.
-彻奇那呢  -试过了
-Try over at Chalky's. -I did.
洛莉 斯坦曼也试了
Lolly Steinman as well.
还有纽约的那个姑娘
Chippy in New York,then.
肯特小姐也没见到他
Miss Kent has not seen him either.
这次罗斯坦的货有多少
How many for Rothstein?
八百箱 和上次一样
800. Same as last time.
我不会这么做的 米奇
I wouldn't do this,Mickey.
你当然不会这么做 因为你说了不算
Of course you wouldn't. 'Cause you're not in charge.
动动脑子吧
Use your head,will you?
备用路线不能用 也不能走塔博尔高地
There's no way through the back roads and Tabor Heights is off-limits.
有治安官呢 你自己也听到了
Sheriff's on it. You heard him yourself.
治安官才刚上任不到一周
The sheriff's been on the job less than a week.
而上一个被人活活烧死了
And the last one got burned...
你不需要去装车吗
Don't you have some trucks to load?
当然 老板
Sure thing,boss.
-什么 你听到什么了没  -没有
-What,you hear something? -No,I didn't hear anything.
也睡不着吗
Couldn't sleep either?
床不舒服
Not exactly a featherbed.
就算舒服也睡不好
Although that hasn't been helping either.
貌似对他没什么影响
Doesn't seem to bother him.
我都不知道什么对他有影响
I'm not sure what does.
曾度过了几个像这样的夜晚
More than a few nights spent like this
在阿尔斯特(爱尔兰北部)的时候
back in Ulster.
为什么
How's that?
你得到命令 这样那样的地址
You'd get your orders,this or that address,
然后静静等待 直到完成任务
and then count off the hours till you finish the business.
任务倒不难
Wasn't the work,though.
难的是等待
It was the waiting.
你一定找到打发时间的方法了吧
Must have had your way of getting through it.
是的
Oh,aye.
走在科尔雷恩大街上
Walk through the streets of Coleraine
脑中构想的
in my head.
去学校
Steps to the school.
去教堂 去蔬菜商店
Steps to the church. Steps to the greengrocer.
你一晚上就想这个了
That what you've been doing all night?
我已数月没想过了
I have not thought on the place in months.
听上去 好像你有在家的感觉
Sounds like you're feeling at home.
我知道谁说了算 汤普森先生
I know who's in charge,Mr. Thompson.
也许你对现状不太满意
Maybe you're not happy about it.
我满意与否不重要
It's not my satisfaction that matters.
我是怎么赢得你的忠诚的
And what have I done to earn your loyalty?
你给了我一个位置
You made a place for me.
不说奉承话
Now minus the soft soap.
你至少还给我工钱
You pay me.
天啊
Jesus.
发生了什么
What the fuck happened?
-乔 米勒  -谁
-Joe Miller. -Who?
奥巴尼恩的人
O'Banion's man.
昨晚我在收钱
Last night I was making my collection,
他偷袭我
he dry-gulched me.
他趁你不注意打你吗
What,he hit you when you wasn't looking?
我刚要离开凯勒的酒吧
I was leaving the bar at Keller's.
-他来南边了吗  -用啤酒杯揍的我
-He's on the South Side? -Cracked me with a beer mug.
把我脑袋砸开花了
Split my head open.
该死的爱尔兰混蛋
Irish fucking prick.
他还取笑我
Al,he made fun of me.
-什么  -我的意思是 他...
-What? -I mean,he...
在所有人面前
in front of everybody.
你觉得我自己不烦吗
You think it doesn't bother me?
我身上就是这个味
I can't help how I smell.
不管我怎么洗
Hour after I wash,
怎么换衣服
I already got to change my...
阿尔
Al?
女性健康诊所 圣特雷萨医院
Women's health clinic. St. Theresa's Hospital.
完全免费 女性健康诊所
Free to all. Women's health clinic.
圣特雷萨医院 完全免费
St. Theresa's Hospital. Free to all.
女士 看一下吗
Ma'am,may I give you one of these?
-是小姐  -什么
-Miss. -Pardon?
是小姐 这不是我的孩子
Miss. It's not my baby.
有没有孩子都可以来的
You're welcome in any case.
不好意思 我是圣特雷萨...
Excuse me,I'm from St. Theresa's Hospi...
席勒夫人 你好
Mrs. Shearer. Hello.
怎么了
Yes?
玛格丽特 汤普森 那天...
Margaret Thompson. We met...
我记得 你要干什么
I remember you. What do you want?
你可能有兴趣
Something that might interest you.
这是一系列课程...
It's a series of classes intended...
-我已经知道了  -是课程吗
-I know about it already. -The class?
你做的事我都知道
All of it.
我也觉得你肯定知道
I thought the same thing myself.
而我这么无知 我觉得很羞愧
And truthfully I'm ashamed by my ignorance.
那你凭什么给别人上课
Then who are you to lecture people about it?
不是我上课 是医院的医生
I'm not. We have a doctor from the hospital staff.
请尽量来吧
Please come if you can.
你的经历是很宝贵的...
Your own experience will be valuable for...
每个人都花了两美分吗
A two-cent piece for each of them?
一个月就这一次 这是谁
It's only once a month. Who's this?
医院里的一位女士
A lady from the hospital.
-席勒先生吗  -没错
-Is it Mr. Shearer? -Yes,ma'am.
跟我们的账单有关吧
This isn't about our bill,is it?
我知道我们还的不太及时 但我保证...
We got ourselves a little behind,but I promise...
不是的
No,not that at all.
我是想告诉您太太...
I just wanted to tell your wife that...
看到她恢复得这么好 我很开心
that I'm glad to see she's doing so much better.
我们一直在祈祷
Well,we've said our prayers,
看来上帝是听到了
but that's how the Lord must have wanted it.
是啊
Yes,of course.
他没让埃德温纳降临人世 减轻我们的负担
But He spared Edwina and we're blessed for that.
医生也帮了不少忙
The doctors had some hand in it.
我请了一个星期的假 就为了照顾她
I took the week off to see her through.
你是想偷个懒 抽你那个破雪茄
You just wanted to put your feet up and smoke those awful cigars.
等她完全康复了 我们再要一个
And when she's up to it,we'll try again.
当然也感谢你的好意
We do appreciate your good wishes,though.
我们还回不回去了
Are we gonna spend the whole day out here?
跟着妈妈走
Lead on,Mother.
准备好了吗 小伙子们
Ready,boys?
女性健康课程 圣特雷萨医院 完全免费
Women's health class. St. Theresa's Hospital. Free to all.
女性健康课程 圣特雷萨医院
Women's health class. St. Theresa's Hospital.
花花公子驾到
最近怎么样 乔
我能怎么样
事情都发展到这步田地了
请坐吧
上面还有你的名字呢(幸运之座)
听着像墓碑
不会的 今天不会发生这样的事
我来说说你们犹太人...
对犹太人而言 生意就是生意
而我们做生意投入感情
因为我们有宽阔的胸怀
这是我的地盘
我们都知道
赌场有你的分红 中间人和卖酒都有你的分红
You get a cut in card game,a cut of the fence,a cut of the booze.
海洛因的分红我没有
怎么分 那就是个副业
What's to give? It's a sideline.
你在我地盘上做买卖
然后坐享其成
多还是少 我不在乎
我们心胸宽广
那分你百分之二
我要你所有收入的百分之二
你地盘上的买卖分你百分之二
发生了那破事之后 就这么打发我吗
我们是在讲理
"我们" "我们"
"We." "We."
好好看看
Have a look around.
就咱们俩
There's just you and me.
我有合作伙伴
I have partners.
犹太人 信得过吗
你刚说过生意就是生意
因为犹太人没有心胸
你倒是没摊上事 是吗
下次可能就不是了
下次你就跑不了了是吗
我倒觉得挺好的
我很担心你 萨尔瓦多
我一直是老样子
以前那个经常来的小男孩
野心是有
但很懂得尊重人
但那个孩子哪去了
你身上根本没有他的影子了
百分之三
百分之三十
所有的吗
只有我地盘上的
我们相隔太远了 乔
其实根本不远 萨尔瓦多
只有两英尺
我回去商量一下
该做什么尽管去做
但要记住
罗斯坦 还有那个兰斯基
没有心胸
他们会在背后中伤你
因为他们不是你的家人
等你需要帮助的时候
百分之三十的钱
根本不够用
...gonna look very cheap.
多伊尔先生 我为什么在跟你谈话
Mr. Doyle. Why am I talking to you?
因为你给我打电话了
'Cause you called me.
那我为什么要给你打电话呢
But why am I calling you?
我怎么可能给你打电话呢
Why is that even occurring?
如果你老板如约把酒送过来
If I had my liquor on the timely basis your employer promised,
其实 我若能找到你那
if,in fact,I could reach your employer,
无视商业原则
who now seems to think acceptable business practice
无故消失数天的老板
to disappear for days on end,
我现在就用不着给你打电话了
this conversation would not be taking place.
这样我就会...
And that would make me...
很开心
very happy.
我知道
Yeah,I understand.
-罗斯坦先生  -我掏钱了 我要货
-Listen,Mr. Rothstein. -I want what I paid for.
-现在就要  -没问题 先生
-I want it now. -Okay,sir.
而且我再也不想跟你谈话了
And I don't ever want to find myself chatting with you again.
-当然  -听明白了吗
-Of course. -Is that clear?
明早就送到
You'll have it by tomorrow morning.
罗斯坦那家伙 笑面虎一个
That Rothstein,warm as a lizard.
他说什么了
What did he say?
他在等我们送货
That he's expecting his delivery.
你怎么说的
And what did you tell him?
你说呢 肯定说马上到
That it's coming. What do you think?
我说你是个白痴
What do I think? That you're a fucking idiot.
注意点 伊莱 我是你老板
Watch your step,Eli. I'm your boss.
纳吉特别提到要避开塔博尔高地
Nucky explicitly said to avoid Tabor Heights.
我听到了 但是不可能走备用路线
I heard. There's no way to use the back roads.
最早也要等到五月
Not till May at the earliest.
那就先别送货
So hold off making the delivery.
然后让你哥哥来找我的麻烦吗 不用了
And get your brother's foot up my ass? No,thanks.
我给你说 别这么干 米奇
I'm telling you not to do this,Mickey.
我什么也不做 是他们要做
I'm not doing nothing. They are.
你直接送货去纽约
You're straight through to New York.
在塔博尔高地加大油门 就这样
Gas up in Tabor Heights and that's it.
遇到任何情况都不要停车 就算是警察
You stop for nobody. Not even the law.
今晚是我的夜晚
Tonight is my night.
他有枪
He's got a gun.
好了 好了
Easy!
停手
Stop!
要找那些无力保护自己的人的麻烦吗
You want to pick on people who can't defend themselves?
是吗
Huh?
给他办葬礼的钱
Pay for his funeral.
他们说什么
What are they saying?
他们要收工走人了
I think they're wrapping it up.
他们走了
They're gone.
差点拉了裤子 是吧 孩子
Nearly shit your breeches there,didn't you,son?
该死的 我可不害怕
Heck,I wasn't scared.
我害怕
I was.
好吧 我也怕
Okay,I was,too.
我绝不偷看
There'll not be a peep from me.
他总是这么有意思吗
He always this much fun?
你该听听他是怎么打电话的
You should hear him on the phone sometime.
和他女朋友两情缱绻
...Canoodling with his girlfriend.
冰箱里有培根和鸡蛋
Well,I got bacon and eggs in the icebox.
饿的话 我可以给你们炸一下
I can fry 'em up if anyone's hungry.
也许他们在楼上还留下点酒
Maybe they left a bottle upstairs.
我们来了
Here we are.
来
Come on.
伙计们 准备好赚点钱了吗
Hey,fellas. Ready to make some dough?
吉普点头之前别行动
Don't make a move until Gyp says so.
你们来帮我们封锁道路
You're gonna help us block the road.
开第一枪 然后行动
First shot,then you move.
一定要保证道路封锁
Just keep the road blocked.
-别害怕  -躲起来
-Don't be yellow now. -Down in the shadows.
罗斯坦的货在路上
Rothstein's shipment is on its way.
哪条路
By which route?
塔博尔高地
Tabor Heights.
有消息说这套路是安全的
Word came back it's clear.
没人想知道这二十四小时我们在哪
Did anyone wonder where we were for the last 24 hours?
就算有 他们也没声张
If they did,they were quiet about it.
那么
Well?
你看到了吗
You see this?
看什么 这里什么都没有
See what? There's nothing here.
那就对了 你我都一无所有了
That's my point. We've both got empty hands.
这告诉你什么
What's that say to you?
找个更好的藏身处吗
Find a better hideout?
汤普森先生
Mr. Thompson,
你必须得承认我很擅长这个
you got to admit I'm pretty good at this.
我可不会到处吹嘘
I wouldn't go boasting about it.
是的 我会说我再也不会这么做了
Yeah,and I could say I'd never do it again,
但你不会相信我的 对吧
but you wouldn't believe me,would you?
很可能不会
Probably not.
那么
So...
我为你工作怎么样
so how's about I come work for you?
说来听听 罗兰
How would that go,Rowland?
就...
Well...
让我开车 给我发支枪
put me behind the wheel,box of shotgun shells,
看他们还敢不敢再偷了
just let them try stealing then.
他不喜欢我
He doesn't like me.
你能怨他吗
Can you blame him?
我在紧要关头不淡定吗
Ain't I cool in a tight spot?
你行
You'll do.
我了解这附近的路
I know all the roads around here.
潜伏的好地方
Best places to lie low.
藏东西的好地方
Best places to keep your stash.
他们抓不到我
They won't ever catch me.
我们抓到你了 罗兰
We caught you,Rowland.
是的 但没那么容易
Okay,but it wasn't easy.
瓦克西 戈登 远远没有你那么聪明
And Waxey Gordon,he ain't nearly as smart as you.
他的酒 你想拿多少就拿多少
You could take as much of his booze as you'd like.
轻而易举
It's apples off a tree.
告诉我你想怎么做
Just tell me what you want to do.
你小子很有勇气
You've sure got a lot of moxie.
要不然还有什么办法成功
How else are you supposed to get ahead?
我以为你不抽烟
I thought you didn't smoke.
我说过吗
Did I say that?
-你到底多大了  -十九
-How old are you really? -19.
所以法律上说 我可以开车 这不是更好吗
So legally I'm allowed to drive. Isn't that better?
抽我的
Have one of mine.
-凯斯勒先生  -谁是凯斯勒先生
-Mr. Kessler. -Who's Mr. Kessler?
他是汤普森先生的司机
He's Mr. Thompson's driver.
我以为你会放了他
I thought you were letting him go.
你为什么这么想
Why would you think that?
我误会了
I misunderstood.
现在明白就好
As long as you understand now.
停
Stop!
-那是伊莱吗  -看上去是
-Is that Eli? -Looks like it.
去他的 米奇说看见谁都不停
Fuck that. Mickey said don't stop for nobody.
停车
Stop!
有埋伏 等等
It's an ambush! Wait!
等等 停车
Wait! Stop!
停车 有埋伏
Stop! It's an ambush!
该死 有埋伏
It's a fucking ambush!
有埋伏
在那 在他的大衣里
Oh,right there. Right under his coat.
看看这个 你想要那个吗
Look at this. You want that?
我们把这些扔到哪
Where we dumping these?
上司说在森林里挖个坑
Boss says dig a pit in the woods.
那得花整晚
That'll take all night.
找个偏僻小村
Get the podunks to do it.
天啊 这家伙拉裤子了
Jeez,this one crapped his pants.
我需要个钱包
I need a wallet.
哪个女服务员更可爱一点
Which one of them waitresses do you think is cuter?
短发的那个小女人
The little one with the bobbed hair.
我要和那个红头发的上床
I'm gonna fuck the redhead.
看我
Look.
来 起来
Come on. Come on.
过来 我们弹这个 来
Come on. Here we go. Come on.
纳吉
Nucky.
凯利 邓肯坠机残骸在约塞米蒂国家公园附近找到 女飞行员不幸罹难
我要和你谈谈
I have to talk to you.
我们谈过了
We've had our conversation.
有别的事
This is about something else.
你得听听
And you're gonna need to hear it.